The Guide to the Jerome Charyn Papers 1937-1997 MSS.044
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IX: Typescripts and Galleys
  - Blue Eyes - A Film Treatment By Steve Kesten, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Blue Eyes - Screenplay, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Blue Eyes - Setting Copy - pp 1-149, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Blue Eyes - Setting Copy - pp 150 - 307 (end), undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Blue Eyes - Wonderboy (early version) - Assorted Pages, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Blue Eyes - Wonderboy - Photocopy - pp 1- 99, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Blue Eyes - Wonderboy - Fragment - pp 210-232, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Blue Eyes - Wonderboy - Typescript, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Blue Eyes - Wonderboy - Typescript with Corrections - pp 1-99, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Blue Eyes - Wonderboy - Typescript with Corrections - pp 100 - 232, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Blue Eyes - Wonderboy - Typescript with Variants and Alternative Pages - pp 1-150, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Blue Eyes - Wonderboy - Typescript with Variants and Alternative Pages - pp 150 - 196e, undated; 31142040613658 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Capitaine Kidd - Galleys (French), undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - The Catfish Man - Assorted Pages, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - The Catfish Man - Dead Pages, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - The Catfish Man - Dead Pages, replaced by author on 9/25/1979, 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - The Catfish Man - Edited Typescript, pp. 1-149, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - The Catfish Man - Edited Typescript, pp. 150-299, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - The Catfish Man - Edited Typescript, pp. 300-471 (end), undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - The Catfish Man - Edited Typescript No. 2, pp. 1-197, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - The Catfish Man - Edited Typescript No. 2, pp. 198-471 (end), undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - The Catfish Man - Early Short Stories - Catfish and Crotona Y or Bodybuilding in America / Catfish and Mississippi Mud, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - The Catfish Man - Early Short Stories - Ping-Pong in New York, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - The Catfish Man - Early Short Stories - Soldiers' Hotel, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - The Catfish Man - Fragment - pp 316-318, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - The Catfish Man - Fragment (edited) - pp. 281-311, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - The Catfish Man - Photoset Copy - pp. 1-150, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - The Catfish Man - Photoset Copy - pp. 151-313 (end), undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - The Catfish Man - Setting Copy - pp. 1-197, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - The Catfish Man - Setting Copy - pp. 198-371, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - The Catfish Man - Setting Copy - pp. 372-471 (end) + notes, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - The Changeling - Typescript, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - A Child's History of the Bronx - Assorted Pages, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - A Child's History of the Bronx - Edited Typescript, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - A Child's History of the Bronx - Edited Typescript, Shem + Shaun pp. 1-99, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - A Child's History of the Bronx - Edited Typescript, Shaun, pp 100 - 303 (end), undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - A Child's History of the Bronx - Gunsel (Version of Shem) - Typescript, undated; 31142040613666 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - A Child's History of the Bronx - Little Waldo (Shem) + Archimedes (Shaun) - Typescript, undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - A Child's History of the Bronx - Photocopy of Typescript, Shem + Shaun pp 1 - 99, undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - A Child's History of the Bronx - Photocopy of Typescript, Shem + Shaun pp 100 - 303 (end), undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - A Child's History of the Bronx - Shaun - Edited Typescript, undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - A Child's History of the Bronx - Shem - Typescript, undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - A Child's History of the Bronx - Typescript, undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Citizen Sidel - Edited Typescript, undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Citizen Sidel - Final Typescipt + notes, undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Close Encounters of an Unexpected Kind - Typescript, undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Coen in Love - Edited Typescript, undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Coen in Love - Typescript - Typescript + Rejection Note from The Village Voice, undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Crayola Detective (Founder's Day) - Early version of the screenplay - Typescript, undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Crayola Detective (Founder's Day) - Typescript, undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Darlin' Bill - Assorted Pages, undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Darlin' Bill - Early Version - pp. 1-197, undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Darlin' Bill - Early Version - pp. 198-426 (end), undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Darlin' Bill - Edited Typescript - pp. 1-197, with variants, undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Darlin' Bill - Edited Typescript - pp. 198-426 (end), undated; 31142040613674 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Darlin' Bill - Edited Typescript - Final - pp. 1-197, undated; 31142040613682 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Darlin' Bill - Edited Typescript - Final - pp. 198-426 (end), undated; 31142040613682 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - David and Goliath - 5 Typescripts + Rejection Letters from Midstream and Esquire., undated; 31142040613682 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Dumah - Typescript + note from Curtis Publishing Co., undated; 31142040613682 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - The Education of Patrick Silver - Edited Typescript, undated; 31142040613682 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - The Education of Patrick Silver - Galleys, undated; 31142040613682 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Eisenhower, My Eisenhower - Setting Copy - pp. 1-149, undated; 31142040613682 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Eisenhower, My Eisenhower - Setting Copy - pp. 150-220 (end) + notes, undated; 31142040613682 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Eisenhower, My Eisenhower - Setting Copy - Enclosures, undated; 31142040613682 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Eisenhower, My Eisenhower - Typescript - 1 of 2, undated; 31142040613682 (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Eisenhower, My Eisenhower - Typescript - 2 of 2, undated; 31142040613682 (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - El Bronx - Edited Typescript, undated; 31142040613682 (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - El Bronx - Galleys, undated; 31142040613682 (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - El Bronx - Setting Copy, undated; 31142040613682 (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - El Bronx - Typescript (with the original version of short story Alyosha), undated; 31142040613682 (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - Elsinore - Edited Typescript, undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - Elsinore - Final Typescript, undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - Emissary - Edited Typescript + Rejection letter from Commentary (1962), 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - Farewell!...Farewell!.. - 3 Typescripts + Rejection letter from Commentary (1962), 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 91)
  - Farewell!...Farewell!.. - 2 Old Versions - Typescripts, undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 92)
  - Fitzgerald - Typescript, undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 93)
  - The Franklin Scare - Edited Typescript, pp. 1-199, undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 94)
  - The Franklin Scare - Edited Typescript, pp. 200-392 (end), undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 95)
  - The Franklin Scare - Franklin's Other Child - I (pp. 1-227), undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 96)
  - The Franklin Scare - Franklin's Other Child - II-III (pp. 228-426), undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 97)
  - The Franklin Scare - Photoset Copy - pp. 1 - 130, undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 98)
  - The Franklin Scare - Photoset Copy - pp. 131 - 326 (end), undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 99)
  - The Franklin Scare - Setting Copy - pp. 1-199, undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - The Franklin Scare - Setting Copy - pp. 200 - 392, undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 101)
  - The Geek of New York -Edited Typescript + Fragment, undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 102)
  - The Giant, the Pirate and the Greek - Typescript, undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 103)
  - God Bless Captain Eddie and Private Ming - 3 typescripts, undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 104)
  - The Good Policeman - Edited Typescipt, pp. 1-149 + notes and list of corrections, undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 105)
  - The Good Policeman - Edited Typescipt, pp. 150-346 (end), undated; 31142040613690 (Box 18, Folder 106)
  - Gunsel - Typescript + note from Gordon Lish (Esquire), undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 107)
  - Harry in Gehinnom - Edited Typescript - 1 of 2, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 108)
  - Harry in Gehinnom - Edited Typescript - 2 of 2, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 109)
  - Harry in Gehinnom - Typescript, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 110)
  - Harvey - 2 Edited Typescripts, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 111)
  - Hey, Joe DiMaggio, Why Don't You Talk To Me - Typescript, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 112)
  - Imberman/Farewell!...Farewell!... - Drafts, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 113)
  - Imberman - Typescript, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 114)
  - In Memorium, November 21 - 2 Typescripts, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 115)
  - Investigations - Typescript, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 116)
  - King Jude - Assorted Typescript and Manuscript pages - 1 of 2, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 117)
  - King Jude - Assorted Typescript and Manuscript pages - 2 of 2, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 118)
  - King Jude - Edited Typescript - 1 of 2 - pp. 1-199, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 119)
  - King Jude - Edited Typescript - 1 of 2 - pp. 200-? (end), undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 120)
  - King Jude - Edited Typescript - 2 of 2 - pp. 1-199, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 121)
  - King Jude - Edited Typescript - 2 of 2 - pp. 200-? (end), undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 122)
  - King Jude - Typescript - pp. 1-199, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 123)
  - King Jude - Typescript - pp. 200-420 (end), undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 124)
  - King Jude - Typescript Fragment - pp. 1-92, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 125)
  - King Jude - Typescript Fragments, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 126)
  - Little Angel Street - Edited Typescript, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 127)
  - Little Angel Street - Galleys, undated; 31142040613708 (Box 19, Folder 128)
  - Little Angel Street - Setting Copy, undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 129)
  - Little Things - Typescript, undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 130)
  - The Man Who Grew Younger - Edited typescript + rejection letter from Commentary (1963), undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 131)
  - The Man Who Grew Younger And Other Stories - Edited typescript, undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 132)
  - The Man Who Grew Younger And Other Stories - Galleys - 1st Pass, undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 133)
  - The Man Who Grew Younger And Other Stories - Galleys - 2nd Pass, undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 134)
  - The Man Who Grew Younger And Other Stories - Sample Pages for Harper & Row., undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 135)
  - Maria's Girls - Galleys - Master Set - 1st Pass, undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 136)
  - Maria's Girls - Edited Typescript - pp. 1-245, undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 137)
  - Maria's Girls - Edited Typescript - pp. 246-367 (end), undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 138)
  - Maria's Girls - Setting Copy - pp. 1-205, undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 139)
  - Maria's Girls - Setting Copy - pp. 206-367 (end), undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 140)
  - Marylin, the Wild - Edited Typescript - pp. 1-149, undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 141)
  - Marylin, the Wild - Edited Typescript - pp. 150-276 (end), undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 142)
  - Marylin, the Wild - Galleys, undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 143)
  - Marylin, the Wild - Setting Copy - pp. 1-149, undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 144)
  - Marylin, the Wild - Setting Copy - pp. 150-276 (end), undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 145)
  - Marylin, the Wild - Typescript Fragment - pp. 129-237, undated; 31142040613716 (Box 20, Folder 146)
  - Marylin, the Wild - Typescript - Hy Cohen's Copy - pp. 1-149, undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 147)
  - Marylin, the Wild - Typescript - Hy Cohen's Copy - pp. 150-273 (end), undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 148)
  - Marylin, the Wild - Typescript - pp. 1-154, undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 149)
  - Marylin, the Wild - Typescript - pp. 154a-271 (end), undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 150)
  - Marylin, the Wild - Typescript with variants - pp. 1-231, undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 151)
  - Metropolis - Edited Typescript - pp 1-199, undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 152)
  - Metropolis - Edited Typescript - pp 200-397 (end), undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 153)
  - Mitka the Thief - Edited Typescript, undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 154)
  - Montezuma's Man - Edited Typescript - pp. 1-144, undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 155)
  - Montezuma's Man - Edited Typescript - pp. 145-323 (end), undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 156)
  - Montezuma's Man - Galleys - pp. 1-153, undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 157)
  - Montezuma's Man - Galleys - pp. 154-277, undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 158)
  - Montezuma's Man - Setting Copy - pp. 1-200, undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 159)
  - Montezuma's Man - Setting Copy - pp. 201-353 (end), undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 160)
  - Movieland - Edited Typescript - pp. 1-194, undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 161)
  - Movieland - Edited Typescript - pp. 195-354, undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 162)
  - Movieland - Edited Typescript - pp. 355-449 (end) + notes, undated; 31142040613724 (Box 21, Folder 163)
  - Movieland - Galleys - pp. 1-149, undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 164)
  - Movieland - Galleys - pp. 150-293(end), undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 165)
  - Movieland - Page Proofs - Samplings, undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 166)
  - Movieland - Typescript - p 1-199, undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 167)
  - Movieland - Typescript - p 200-399, undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 168)
  - Movieland - Typescript - p 400-481 (end), undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 169)
  - Nightfall - Edited Typescript, undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 170)
  - New York - Typescript, undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 171)
  - Once Upon A Droshky - Fragments and Notes, undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 172)
  - Once Upon A Droshky - Chapters - Typescript, undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 173)
  - On the Darkening Green - Edited Typescript - chs. 1-7 (end), undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 174)
  - On the Darkening Green - Edited Typescript - chs. 8-19 (end), undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 175)
  - On the Darkening Green - Galleys, undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 176)
  - Panna Maria - Assorted Pages, undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 177)
  - Panna Maria - Edited Typescript - pp. 1-200, undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 178)
  - Panna Maria - Edited Typescript - pp. 201-403, undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 179)
  - Panna Maria - Edited Typescript - pp. 404-598, undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 180)
  - Panna Maria - Edited Typescript - pp. 599-824 (end), undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 181)
  - Panna Maria - Galleys - Master Set - 1st Pass - pp. 1-194, undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 182)
  - Panna Maria - Galleys - Master Set - 1st Pass - pp. 195-447 (end), undated; 31142040613732 (Box 22, Folder 183)
  - Panna Maria - Galleys - Master Set- 2nd Pass - pp. 1-193, undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 184)
  - Panna Maria - Galleys - Master Set- 2nd Pass - pp. 194-447 (end), undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 185)
  - Paradize Man - Edited Typescript - pp. 1-200, undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 186)
  - Paradize Man - Edited Typescript - pp. 201-329 (end), undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 187)
  - Paradize Man - Galleys, undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 188)
  - Paris, New York and John Cowper Powys - 2 typescripts, drafts + rejection letter from The New York Times., undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 189)
  - Patrick - Typescript, undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 190)
  - Pinocchio's Nose - Assorted Pages with Variants and Corrections - 1 of 2, undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 191)
  - Pinocchio's Nose - Assorted Pages with Variants and Corrections - 2 of 2, undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 192)
  - Pinocchio's Nose - Edited Typescript - Early Verion - pp. 1-199, undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 193)
  - Pinocchio's Nose - Edited Typescript - Early Verion - pp. 199-415, undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 194)
  - Pinocchio's Nose - Edited Typescript with Variants, pp. 1-199, undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 195)
  - Pinocchio's Nose - Edited Typescript with Variants, pp. 200-399, undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 196)
  - Pinocchio's Nose - Edited Typescript with Variants, pp. 400-642 (end), undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 197)
  - Pinocchio's Nose - Galleys - Master Set - 1st Pass - pp. 1-199, undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 198)
  - Pinocchio's Nose - Galleys - Master Set - 1st Pass - pp. 200-384 (end), undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 199)
  - Pinocchio's Nose - Galleys - Master Set - 2nd Pass - pp. 1-199, undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 200)
  - Pinocchio's Nose - Galleys - Master Set - 2nd Pass - pp. 200-384 (end), undated; 31142040613740 (Box 23, Folder 201)
  - Pinocchio's Nose - Photoset Copy - pp. 1-192, undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 202)
  - Pinocchio's Nose - Photoset Copy - pp. 193-384 (end), undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 203)
  - Pinocchio's Nose - Typescript - pp. 1-199, undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 204)
  - Pinocchio's Nose - Typescript - pp. 200-399, undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 205)
  - Pinocchio's Nose - Typescript - pp. 400-642 (end), undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 206)
  - Race Day at Hiawatha - Edited Typescript, undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 207)
  - The Same Mrs. Warpole - Edited Typescript, undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 208)
  - Secret Isaac - Arbor House Materials, undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 209)
  - Secret Isaac - Edited Typescript - pp. 1-249, undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 210)
  - Secret Isaac - Edited Typescript - pp. 250-332 (end), undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 211)
  - Secret Isaac - Galleys - Cut Pages, undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 212)
  - Secret Isaac - Galleys - Uncut Pages, undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 213)
  - Secret Isaac - Photoset Copy (mixed pages) - 1 of 3, undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 214)
  - Secret Isaac - Photoset Copy (mixed pages) - 2 of 3, undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 215)
  - Secret Isaac - Photoset Copy (mixed pages) - 3 of 3, undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 216)
  - Secret Isaac - Setting Copy with Corrections, pp. 1-149, undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 217)
  - Secret Isaac - Setting Copy with Corrections, pp. 150-end, undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 218)
  - The Seventh Babe - Edited Typescript - pp. 1-199, undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 219)
  - The Seventh Babe - Edited Typescript - pp. 200-399 (end), undated; 31142040613757 (Box 24, Folder 220)
  - The Seventh Babe - Master Set Copy - pp. 1-199, undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 221)
  - The Seventh Babe - Master Set Copy - pp. 200-399 (end), undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 222)
  - The Seventh Babe - Photoset Copy - pp. 1-241, 1979; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 223)
  - The Seventh Babe - Photoset Copy - pp. 242-446 (end), 1979; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 224)
  - The Seventh Babe - Replacement Pages, undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 225)
  - The Seventh Babe - Revised Pages, undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 226)
  - The Seventh Babe - Copy - pp. 1-199, undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 227A)
  - The Seventh Babe - Setting Copy - pp. 200-399 (end), undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 227B)
  - The Shidach - Typescripts + Rejection Letter from The New Yorker, undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 228)
  - The Tar Baby - Assorted Pages with Corrections + Notes, undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 229)
  - The Tar Baby - Galleys + Publisher's Memo, 1972; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 230)
  - The Tar Baby - Photocopy of Typescript with Corrections, undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 231)
  - The Tar Baby - Setting Copy - pp.1-149, undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 232)
  - The Tar Baby - Setting Copy - pp. 150-269 (end), undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 233)
  - The Tar Baby - Typescript - pp.1-149, undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 234)
  - The Tar Baby - Typescript - pp. 150-269 (end), undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 235)
  - The Tar Baby - Typescript - Enclosures, undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 236)
  - Untitled Drafts and Fragments - Edited Typescripts, undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 237)
  - War Cries Over Avenue C - Edited Typescript - pp. 1-198, undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 238)
  - War Cries Over Avenue C - Edited Typescript - pp. 199-485 (end), undated; 31142040613765 (Box 25, Folder 239)
  - War Cries over Avenue C - Early version (The Fall of the Magicians) - Assorted Pages, undated; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 240)
  - War Cries over Avenue C - Early version (The Fall of the Magicians) - Edited Typescript - pp. 1-270, undated; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 241)
  - War Cries over Avenue C - Early version (The Fall of the Magicians) - Edited Typescript - pp. 271- 482 (end), undated; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 242)
- Series X: The Good Policeman TV Series
  - Beat Sheet + Notes, 1992; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Pilot Episode - 1st Draft, 1992; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Pilot Episode - Drafts, 1992; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Pilot Episode - Final, 1992; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - 1st Production Draft, 1993; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - 2nd Production Draft, 1993; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Production Documents, 1993; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Schedules, 1993; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Series XI: Publishers Catalogs
  - Arbor House, 1977-1982; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Casterman, 1991-1994; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Claassen, 1988-1998; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Decouvertes Gallimard, 1993-1995; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Folio, 1992-1997; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - La Bibliotheque, 1994; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Marco Tropea Editore, 1996; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 7)